Let's look at the feedforward part first.
我们首先观察前馈部分
To make our computations easier,
为了让计算更加简单
let's decide to have n inputs,
我们确定使用 n 个输入
three neurons in a single hidden layer, and two outputs.
一个隐藏层的 3 个神经元和 2 个输出
By the way, in practice,
顺便说一下 实际上
we can have thousands of neurons in a single hidden layer.
在单个隐藏层中可能有数千个神经元
We will use W_1 as the set of weights from x to h,
我们使用 W1 作为 x 到 h 的一组权重
and W_2 as the set of weights from h to y.
W2 作为 h 到 y 的一组权重
Since we have only one hidden layer,
由于只有一个单独的隐藏层
we will have only two steps in each feedforward cycle.
所以在每个前馈循环中只有两个步骤
Step one, we'll be finding h from a given input and a set of weights W_1.
第一步我们要从特定输入和一组权重 W1 中找出 h
And step two, we'll be finding the output y
第二步我们要从计算后的 h
from the calculated h and the set of weights W_2.
和一组权重 W2 中找出输出 y
You will find that other than the use of non-linear activation functions,
你会发现除了使用非线性激活函数
which I will talk about soon,
我很快要探讨的内容
all of the calculations involve linear combinations of inputs and weights.
所有计算都涉及输入和权重的线性组合
Or in other words, we will use matrix multiplications.
换句话说 我们使用矩阵乘法
Let's start with step number one,
首先我们进行第一步 找到 h
finding h. Notice that if we have more than one neuron in the hidden layer,
注意如果我们隐藏层包括多个神经元
which is usually the case,
通常情况都是如此
h is actually a vector.
实际上 h 是一个向量
We will have our initial inputs x,
我们有初始输入 x
x is also a vector,
x 也是向量
and we want to find the values of the hidden neurons,
我们想要找出隐藏神经元的值 h
h. Each input is connected to each neuron in the hidden layer.
每个输入都连接到隐藏层的每个神经元
For simplicity, we will use the following indices: W_11 connects x_1 to h_1,
为简单起见 我们使用以下指数 W11 连接 x1 和 h1
W_13 connects x_1 to h_3,
W13 连接 x1 和 h3
W_21 connects x_2 to h_1,
W21 连接 x2 和 h1
W_n3 connects x_n to h_3, and so on.
Wn3 连接 xn 和 h3 等等
The vector of the inputs x_1, x_2,
输入向量 x1 x2
all the way up to x_n,
直到 xn
is multiplied by the weight matrix W_1 to give us the hidden neurons.
乘以权重矩阵 W1 得到隐藏神经元
So each vector, h,
那么每个向量 h’
equals vector x multiplied by the weight matrix, W_1.
等于向量 x’ 乘以权重矩阵 W1
In this case, we have a weight matrix with n rows,
在这种情况下 因为有 n 个输入
as we have n inputs,
我们得到 n 行的权重矩阵
and three columns, as we have three neurons in the hidden layer.
因为隐藏层包括 3 个神经元 我们得到三列
If you multiply the input vector by the weight matrix,
如果把输入向量乘以权重矩阵
you will have a simple linear combination for
你会得到隐藏层中每个单元的简单线性组合
each neuron in the hidden layer giving us vector,
从而得到向量 h’
h. So for example,
那么例如
h_1 will be x_1 times W_11,
h’1 等于 x1 乘以 W11
plus x_2 times W_21, and so on.
加上 x2 乘以 W21 等等
But we are not done with calculating the hidden layer yet.
但是我们还没有完成隐藏层的计算
Notice the prime symbol I've been using?
注意到我一直使用的上撇号吗？
I used it to remind us that we are not done with finding h yet.
我用这个符号提醒 我们还没找到 h
We're almost there but not quite yet.
非常接近却没有完成
To make sure that the values of h do not explode or increase too much in size,
为了避免 h 的值激增或增长过大
we need to use an activation function usually denoted by the Greek letter, phi.
我们需要使用激活函数 通常使用希腊字母 φ
We can use a hyperbolic tangent.
我们可以使用双曲正切
Using this function will ensure that our outputs are between one and negative one.
使用这个函数可以确保我们的输出在 1 到 -1 之间
We can also use a sigmoid.
我们也可以使用 sigmoid
Using this function will ensure that our outputs are between one and zero.
使用这个函数可以确保我们的输出在 0 到 1 之间
We can also use a rectified linear unit or in short, a ReLu function,
我们也可以使用修正线性单元 即 ReLu 函数
where the negative values are nulled and the positive values remain as they are.
其中负值为0 正值保持不变
Each activation function has its advantages and disadvantages.
每个激活函数都存在优缺点
What they all share is that they allow the network to represent
他们的共同之处是能让网络
nonlinear relationships between its inputs and its outputs.
体现出输入和输出的非线性关系
And this is very important since most real world data is nonlinear.
这是非常重要的 因为现实世界中大部分数据是非线性的
Mathematically, the linear combination and activation function can simply be written as h
从数学角度来说 线性组合和激活函数可以简单地写成
equals to the output of an activation function of
h 等于输入向量乘以对应权重矩阵的
the input vector multiplied by the corresponding weight matrix.
激活函数的输出结果 即 h = φ (x, W1)
Using these functions can be a bit tricky as they
使用这些函数可能会有点棘手
contribute to the vanishing gradient problem that we mentioned before.
因为它们存在之前提到过的梯度消失问题
But more on this later.
不过随后会进行详细介绍